<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<document>
    <properties>
        <title>Plugin Context Include</title>
    </properties>
    <body>
        <section name="Plugin Context Include">
            <subsection name="Introduction">
                <p>
                    This plugin is used to display a content as an include depending of the parameters of the request.
                </p>
            </subsection>
            <subsection name="Creation/Modification of contextual includes">
                <p>
                    The creation/modification of an include allows the administrator to personnalize the include and to configure
                    the parameter the request must have in order to display the content.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <center>
                        <img src="../images/creation.png" />
                    </center>
                </p>
                <p>
                    The <strong>strict</strong> mode allow to display its content only if the request possesses exactly the configurated parameters.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Example : Let's assume we have one include in strict mode with its parameters configured like this :
                </p>
                <p>
                    <center>
                        <img src="../images/modification.png" />
                    </center>
                </p>
                <p>
                    For URL that has the following parameters :
                </p>
                <div class="source">
                    <pre>
jsp/site/Portal.jsp?page=form&#38;id_form=1
                    </pre>
                </div>
                <p>
                    The content will be displayed
                </p>
                <p>
                    However, for an URL that has the following parameters :
                </p>
                <div class="source">
                    <pre>
jsp/site/Portal.jsp?page=form
                    </pre>
                </div>
                <p>
                    or the following parameters :
                </p>
                <div class="source">
                    <pre>
jsp/site/Portal.jsp?page=form&#38;id_form=1&#38;action=save
                    </pre>
                </div>
                <p>
                    the content will not be displayed
                </p>
            </subsection>
            <subsection name="Plugin configuration">
            <p>
                The plugin configuration is handled in the back office, in the plugin advanced parameters.
            </p>
            <p>
                <center>
                    <img src="../images/advanced_parameters.png" />
                </center>
            </p>
            </subsection>
            <subsection name="Cumulation mode">
                <p>
                    The cumulation mode is used to insert several inclludes and to be able to position the includes in the template.
                </p>
                <p>
                    To use the HTML inclusion service, one must add in the main template (<strong>page_frameset.html</strong>) the following bookmark :
                </p>
                <div class="source">
                    <pre>
contextinclude_&lt;id_context&gt;!
                    </pre>
                </div>
                <p>
                    where <strong>id_context</strong> matches the id of the context include.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Note : the plugin also provides the label freemarker to insert in the template.
                </p>
                <p>
                    <center>
                        <img src="../images/id_context.png" />
                    </center>
                </p>
            </subsection>
            <subsection name="Without cumulation mode">
                <p>
                    The mode without cumulation allow to create only one include. Every include use the same label freemarker.
                </p>
                <p>
                    To use the HTML code inclusion service, one must add in the main templlate(<strong>page_frameset.html</strong>) the following bookmark :
                </p>
                <div class="source">
                    <pre>
contextinclude!
                    </pre>
                </div>
                <p>
                    Note : Since it only displays one include, the performance are better than the mode with cumulation.
                </p>
                <p>
                    Note 2 : The display order is really important in this mode. Indeed, since this plugin only displays one include,
                    only the first include that verifies the parameters will be displayed.
                </p>
            </subsection>
        </section>	
    </body>
</document>